http://www.cannibal.com.au/pages/privacy-policy

PRIVACY POLICY
We want you to have a belief in Cannibal products. We therefore respect your privacy, will look after the information you provide us and will strive to use it in accordance with your wishes. This policy is provided so that you know how we treat the information we receive from you.
Collection and use of InformationPersonal information such as names and addresses, may be collected and held. This information is used to provide customers and others with products and services. This information is also used to administer competitions and promotional campaigns, inform customers of special offers or new products or to provide information which we believe will be of interest. Unless we are informed otherwise, we will continue to use the information collected in this way. You can ask to be removed from our mailing lists at any time by emailing custom@cannibal.com.au with the word “unsubscribe” in the subject line. Normally we collect information from the persons concerned and they are under no obligation to provide it. However, without certain information we may be unable to provide the products or services requested.
Accuracy of InformationAccuracy of information is important to us and changes or corrections to information held will be welcomed at any time. You have the right to gain access to your information at any time.
Security of InformationMost personal information is stored in-house. All reasonable steps are taken to protect the security of the personal information held, be it stored in electronic or hard copy form. As we value your privacy we will not give or sell your personal information to any other company for use in its marketing or solicitation.
Complaints Concerning Privacy PracticesComplaints concerning the privacy practices or about how personal information is managed, may be forwarded at any time to the Managing Director/CEO. All complaints under this policy will be treated seriously, dealt with promptly in a confidential manner and will not be used to affect the delivery of product to you.
The Internet Is Not Completely SecureUnfortunately no data transmission over the internet is completely secure and while we strive to protect your information there can be no 100% guarantee.
Bound By LawCannibal is bound by the Privacy Act 1998, the associated 10 National Privacy Principles for the handling of personal information and the Spam Act 2003.
Cannibal stands behind its products. Please refer to the Product Guarantee and Returns on our website. There are some obligations on you that you should be aware of:
All orders for the sale of goods are accepted according to the terms and conditions below, Cannibal will supply the goods to you on these terms and conditions. By ordering an item from Cannibal, you expressly agree to these terms and conditions. Cannibal may amend these terms and conditions at any time, and any such amendment will be effective immediately. Your rights as a consumer under the Trade Practices Act are not affected by these terms and conditions.
Follow
TERMS & CONDITIONS
PRIVACY POLICY
CONTACT
Sign up to get the latest on sales, new releases and more …
© 2020 Cannibal Online.
Designed by Out of the Sandbox.
